http://www.bambooflorist.com.my/privacy

Due to the international precautionary measures against Covid-19, our flower shipments may experience delays. In the event of flower unavailability, it will be substituted with a similar flower of equal or higher value while maintaining the overall aesthetics without prior notice.
0
item(s)
Your shopping cart is empty!
Login / Register
My Account
Checkout
Navigation
Home
SHOP ALLHand BouquetFlower BasketGrand OpeningGourmet HamperBloom BoxFlowers & FruitsCondolence FlowersGraduationNew BornFlowers & ChocolatesArtificial ArrangementFlowers & Liquor
Delectable Cakes
Preserved Series
Christmas Collection
CONTACT US
Privacy PolicyBamboo Florist PRIVACY POLICY FOR THE INTERNETBamboo Florist is and attempts to be sensitive to your privacy on the Internet. We will attempt to treat the information that we received from you with reasonable care. Bamboo Florist uses information provided by you (if any) to measure the use of our site and to improve the content of our site. The personal information provided is used by us to respond to your inquiry, process an order or allow you to access specific account information. At times, we will email you or look for you in Facebook with information provided by you to update you with our latest news. We will not release your personal data to any third party outside Bamboo Florist unless compelled by law, with your informed consent, to fulfill an order or request you have given to us, or to protect us against unlawful activity, fraud, or any danger to public safety.
ABOUT US |
NEWS |
DELIVERY |
PRIVACY POLICY |
TERMS &AMP CONDITIONS |
RETURN |
FAQ |
PAYMENT SUBMISSION FORM |
2020.
